[{"answer": "Very good.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "I mean I've had people come up to me in airports.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "When you look back on this career you've had?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "I don't miss the daily of it.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Do you miss the daily connection?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Really, so you didn't repeat very often?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "ONAHUE: Well, you know, it's hard for me to -- I don't want to criticize them, because I took a lot of heat.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What do you think of the way that television has evolved since your daily show stopped?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Yes, and we were always -- I mean we were always different.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "It would be strange if you did approve of it all in a sense, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Oh, well, everybody thought that their kids would catch it if they watched it.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "And what was the reaction to that?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "We had a very good program with Mohamed Ali.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "If I could let you do one again tomorrow, what would it be?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Marlo did a book titled \"The Right Words at the Right Time.\"", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "You know, he was one of the great boxers in history, but he also had this phenomenal brain and humor and self-marketing style which you just -- you don't get that package, do you, very often?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Completely.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "One of many.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "What do you make of the Rick Santorum surge?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "And I'm like, here's a guy who basically repeatedly says I support the constitution.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "He's calling for a nanny government.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "A president says when I get into power, I'm going to make it more available for poor people to have better health care than they're getting already and this is an abject miserable failure that he should be lambasted for?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Well, it is certainly true that -- first of all, I was a single parent.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "When you look back, what do you think?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "I think Oprah has risen to a level in the stratosphere unknown to all of us.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "What do you think of Oprah?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, I think she's -- she's a compelling personality.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "Why, do you think?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Look at my own early history.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "That's a pretty good endorsement, isn't it?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "He would be a better guest I guess than I would.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Try a bit of -- a bit of not dealing with just the friendly fire all the time?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I don't think we'll ever get over it.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "How's it been for you?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "I was thinking that it was a nightmare and that I was going to wake up.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "What are you thinking when this is all unfurling?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "I mean, you I know, John, when you first discovered your daughter was dead, was told did they get the person that did this?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "It definitely did.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "And did it give you any kind of comfort that they had?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "It was very difficult.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Was it cathartic in any sense?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "No, not for me.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Is it hard to reconcile your faith when something like this happens?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Well, we do feel, you know, he was mentally disturbed.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "What are your -- what are your views of him?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "Go to ChristinaTaylorGreen.org, and we have a website.", "docId": "120105pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "And if people want to help, what do they do?", "qSentId": 667}]